

Md. Monjurul Ahsan

Designer & Developer

LANGUAGES

KEY SKILLS



CONTACT

(01721872620



SOCIAL







ABOUT ME

I am a professional graphics designer and I am student currently studying B.SC in CSE. I have 2 years of experience as a freelancer at Fiverr. My speciality is Logo design, UI/UX, Portrait and Line art. Currently I am working on growing my skill in web development.

EDUCATION

University : Daffodil International University Department : Computer Science and Engineering

: 3.61 out of 4.00 (Average) CGPA

: 2020 - 2022Year

Higher Secondary Certificate (H.S.C)

College : Dhaka City College

Group : Science

GPA : 4.75 out of 5.00

Passing Year: 2019

Secondary School Certificate (S.S.C)

School : Bright School and College

Group : Science

GPA : 5.00 out of 5.00

Passing Year: 2017

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Graphic Designer at Fiverr, Since 2020 – present.

Programmer at CPC, Since 2020 - present.

TEAM PROJECT

Android App project – Click & GO (UI/UX design)

Android App project – Social Call (UI/UX design)

Web design project – Newyork Café & Restaurent (UI/UX design)

INTERESTS

VR, AR, Anime, Video Games, Art

ACHIEVEMENTS

Nothing Special